<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>JardinD</title>
  
  
  <link href="https://jardind.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://jardind.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2021-06-13T23:54:38.648Z</updated>
  <id>https://jardind.github.io/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>JardinD</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sonnet 65</title>
    <link href="https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/14/Sonnet-65/"/>
    <id>https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/14/Sonnet-65/</id>
    <published>2021-06-13T23:07:40.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-06-13T23:54:38.648Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Since brass, nor stone, nor earth, nor boundless sea<br>But sad mortality ov’rsways their power.<br>How with this rage shall beauty hold a plea<br>Whose action is no stronger than a flower?<br>O how shall summer’s honey breath hold out<br>Against the wrackful siege of batt’ring days，<br>When rocks impregnable are not so stout,<br>Nor gates of steel so strong, but time decays?<br>O fearful meditation! where, alack<br>Shall time’s best jewel from time’s chest lie hid,<br>Or what strong hand can hold his swift foot back,<br>Or who his spoils of beauty can forbid?<br>O none, unless this miracle have might<br>That in black ink my love may still shine bright.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Since brass, nor stone, nor earth, nor boundless sea&lt;br&gt;But sad mortality ov’rsways their power.&lt;br&gt;How with this rage shall beauty hold </summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Shakespearean" scheme="https://jardind.github.io/tags/Shakespearean/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sonnet 76</title>
    <link href="https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/13/Sonnet-76/"/>
    <id>https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/13/Sonnet-76/</id>
    <published>2021-06-12T23:54:53.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-06-13T00:00:32.994Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Why is my verse so barren of new pride<br>So far from variation or quick change?<br>Why, with the time, do I not glance aside<br>To new-found methods and to compounds strange?<br>Why write I still all-one, ever the same,<br>And keep invention in a noted weed,<br>That every word doth almost tell my name,<br>Showing their birth and where they did proceed.<br>O know, sweet love, I always write of you,<br>And you and love are still my argument.<br>So all my best is dressing old words new,<br>Spending again what is already spent:<br>For, as the sun is daily new and old,<br>So is my love, still telling what is told.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Why is my verse so barren of new pride&lt;br&gt;So far from variation or quick change?&lt;br&gt;Why, with the time, do I not glance aside&lt;br&gt;To new-f</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Shakespearean" scheme="https://jardind.github.io/tags/Shakespearean/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sonnet 98</title>
    <link href="https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/12/Sonnet-98/"/>
    <id>https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/12/Sonnet-98/</id>
    <published>2021-06-12T13:24:01.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-06-12T13:30:47.239Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From you have I been absent in the spring<br>When proud-piled April, dressed in all his trim<br>Hath put a spirit of youth in everything<br>That heavy Saturn laugh’d and leap’d with him<br>Yet nor the lays of birds, nor the sweet smell<br>Of different flowers in odour and in hue<br>Could make me any summer’s story tell<br>Or from the proud lap pluck them where they grew.<br>Nor did I wonder at the lily’s white,<br>Nor praise the deep vermilion of the rose.<br>They were but sweet, but figures of delight,<br>Drawn after you, you pattern of all those.<br>Yet seem’d it winter still, and you away,<br>As with your shadow I with these did play.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;From you have I been absent in the spring&lt;br&gt;When proud-piled April, dressed in all his trim&lt;br&gt;Hath put a spirit of youth in everything&lt;</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Shakespearean" scheme="https://jardind.github.io/tags/Shakespearean/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sonnet 18</title>
    <link href="https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/11/Sonnet-18/"/>
    <id>https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/11/Sonnet-18/</id>
    <published>2021-06-11T01:46:47.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-06-11T01:52:12.399Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Shall I compare thee to a summer’s day?<br>Thou art more lovely and more temperate.<br>Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,<br>And summer’s lease hath all too short a date.<br>Sometime too hot the eye of heaven shines,<br>And often is His gold complexion dimmed.<br>And every fair from fair sometime declines,<br>By chance or Nature’s changing course untrimmed.<br>But thy eternal summer shall not fade,<br>Nor lose poesssion of that fair thou ow’st.<br>Nor shall death brag thou wanderst in his shade,<br>When in eternal lines to time thou grow’st.<br>So long as men can breathe, or eyes can see,<br>So long lives this, and this gives life to thee.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Shall I compare thee to a summer’s day?&lt;br&gt;Thou art more lovely and more temperate.&lt;br&gt;Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May,&lt;br&gt;A</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Shakespearean" scheme="https://jardind.github.io/tags/Shakespearean/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Sonnet 53</title>
    <link href="https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/10/Sonnet-53/"/>
    <id>https://jardind.github.io/2021/06/10/Sonnet-53/</id>
    <published>2021-06-10T04:31:54.000Z</published>
    <updated>2021-06-10T04:40:07.227Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What is your substance, whereof are you made<br>That millions of strange shadows on you tend?<br>Since everyone hath, everyone, one shade,<br>And you, but one, can every shadow lend.<br>Describe Adonis, and the counterfeit<br>Is poorly imitated after you.<br>On Helen’s cheek all art of beauty set,<br>and you in Grecia tires are painted new.<br>Speak of the spring and the foison of the year,<br>The one doth shadow of your beauty show,<br>The other as your bounty doth appear.<br>And in every blessed shape we know.<br>In all external grace you have some part,<br>But you like none, none you, for constant heart.</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;What is your substance, whereof are you made&lt;br&gt;That millions of strange shadows on you tend?&lt;br&gt;Since everyone hath, everyone, one shade</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
    <category term="Shakespearean" scheme="https://jardind.github.io/tags/Shakespearean/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
